<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Final_Year_Project</string>
    <string name="SNA">Discover Your Full Potential
        At Republic Polytechnic (RP), we recognise students with outstanding academic results, leadership qualities and diverse talents. Through our wide range of scholarships and awards, talented students are recognised and encouraged to achieve greater heights!
        As an RP student, you can look forward to a host of scholarships and awards, offered in partnership with our sponsors.</string>
    <string name="FA">RP has various schemes in place to assist students who are unable to afford a polytechnic education.
        At RP, we believe in ensuring that all our students are given equal opportunities to participate in activities that enrich their educational experience.
        Students who need financial assistance can refer to the various schemes below or chat with our FAS Eligibility Chatbot for RP administered schemes.</string>
    <string name="SC">Student Care\n
        There are various categories pertaining to Student Care:\n
        - Counselling\n
        - Mentoring\n
        - Student Insurance\n
        - Special Educational Needs</string>
    <string name="IS">Welcome, International Students!
        As an international student at RP, you will gain knowledge and skills that can lead to exciting careers and further studies opportunities. You will also get to make new friends and experience new cultures.</string>
    <string name="IT">IT Enhanced Learning Experience
        Republic Polytechnic (RP) believes in using Information Technology (IT) to enrich and support the learning experience of all our students.</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan to Find Out More!</string>
    <string name="GRAD">Congratulations to the graduating class of 2023!

Republic Polytechnic (RP) is celebrating this joyous occasion with the graduating cohort, on campus, at The Republic Cultural Centre (TRCC).

Remember to register your attendance for the Graduation Ceremony and register tickets for your family members and friends. If they are unable to attend your graduation ceremony, they may witness the ceremony by viewing the live webcast.</string>
    <string name="MOMNT">Momentum - RP Dance Festival held annually in May, aims to encourage creativity in dance and promote original works of various dance genres.
</string>
    <string name="RF">Reflections - RP Community Arts Festival is a 3-week long festival of music, dance, theatre and visual arts, variety shows, exhibitions or seminars, where local talents are provided with the environment to encourage the creative expressions of various art forms. Due to the current COVID-19 pandemic, the Festival will be brought to the Virtual Space with one physical performance. </string>
</resources>